<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Index on The Office</title>
    <link>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Index on The Office</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 16:46:57 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Communities</title>
      <link>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 16:46:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/communities/</guid>
      <description>Communities #  We will use the Louvain method to divide the network into communities of characters in order to see if we can find some intresting groupings from the network alone.
Methodology #  Results #  This yields 11 communities, which are illustrated in the image below. Each community has a diferent color and labels correspond to the characters that are at the center of each community.
Now let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at the members of each community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Analysis</title>
      <link>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/network_analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 16:46:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/network_analysis/</guid>
      <description>Add plot in/out degree distribution
 Analysis of degree distributions #  Inward degree distribution: We see a power-law distribution, which has a large majority of nodes with few in-going links, and few instances of nodes with large in-going degrees. We can explain this by noting that the main characters overwhelmingly have many ingoing links from more minor characters, without referencing those characters in return. While interacctions with main characters are significant for minor characters, they are insignificant in the storyline of the main-characters, leading to a one-sided relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personality Analysis</title>
      <link>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/personality_analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 16:46:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/personality_analysis/</guid>
      <description>Analysis of the character&amp;rsquo;s personalities #  In this section, we will analyze the characters background based on solely plain text form the wiki pages and their dialogue.
Most descriptive words #  We use the pages from The Office Wiki, for each character to extract some descriptive adjectives and verbs that define the character&amp;rsquo;s background, lifestyle and personality. There are many characters, so we will focus only of the 5 characters with most screen time in The Office, Michael, Dwight, Jim, Pam and Andy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ratings</title>
      <link>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/ratings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 16:46:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/ratings/</guid>
      <description>Ratings per Season #  We overall see the rating climb in seasons 1 and 2, then peak in seasons 3. Season 4 slightly decreases in the averageratings, yet has a much higher variance. Thus the quality between episodes themselves varies much more in this season. We see the decrease in ratings continue until season 7, where it climbs again, before a dramatic decline in season 8.
In the image above, all ratings across all seasons are plotted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Script</title>
      <link>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/script/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 16:46:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/script/</guid>
      <description>The script #  Basic statistics #  We will use a subset of The Office script to gain a deeper analysis of the personality of the characters, their complexity and their interactions with each other.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start by looking into which are the characters that have more lines.
[insert here plot]
We can see that the characters that have the most dialogue are, by far, Michael, Dwight, Jim, Pam and Andy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/sentiment_analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 16:46:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/sentiment_analysis/</guid>
      <description>Sentiment Analysis #  In this section, we will see which characters are the saddest and which are the happiest and which are more emotionally stable and unstable. There is also drama thorughout the season, so we will explore the character&amp;rsquo;s emotional developement for the main characters. Finally, we explore the sentiment evolution throughout the seasons and the saddest and happiest characters.
Sentiment profile of the characters #  From the dialogue, we can analyze the characters&#39; sentiments and determine the distribution of these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viewership</title>
      <link>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/viewership/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 16:46:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/viewership/</guid>
      <description>The first thing we immediately notice is that The Office steadily increases in viewership until season 5. However, it then begins declining in seasons 6 and 7, even before Michael leaves at the end at season 7. In Seasons 8 and 9 where Michael is no longer a part of the cast, the viewership sharply declines until the series ends.
Moreover, we notice a wider variance in viewership in the first seasons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
