<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on The Office</title>
    <link>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on The Office</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 16:46:57 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 16:46:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/about/</guid>
      <description>About #  This website was created by Blanca Robledo Díaz, Oliver Zeman and Natasha Ø. Klingenbrunn as a final project for the course 02805 Social graphs and interactions offered by the Technical University of Denmark.
Each of the following sections will analyse and visualize different datasets relating to the office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Analysis</title>
      <link>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/network_analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 16:46:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/network_analysis/</guid>
      <description>Add plot in/out degree distribution
 Analysis of degree distributions #  Inward degree distribution: We see a power-law distribution, which has a large majority of nodes with few in-going links, and few instances of nodes with large in-going degrees. We can explain this by noting that the main characters overwhelmingly have many ingoing links from more minor characters, without referencing those characters in return. While interacctions with main characters are significant for minor characters, they are insignificant in the storyline of the main-characters, leading to a one-sided relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ratings</title>
      <link>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/ratings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 16:46:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nklingen.github.io/TheOfficeWebsite/docs/ratings/</guid>
      <description>Ratings #   Add ratings per season plot
 We overall see the rating climb in seasons 1 and 2, then peak in seasons 3. Season 4 slightly decreases in the averageratings, yet has a much higher variance. Thus the quality between episodes themselves varies much more in this season. We see the decrease in ratings continue until season 7, where it climbs again, before a dramatic decline in season 8.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
